john carry out the so it was a lot of
the c_i_a_ he told us about the cause of
leon president model who said look we
don't look back we look forward asking
anyone who did it occur
but he did
prosecution jerry opera
uh... who told us about the torture so
if you get your free to go
if you told us about it well even though
a bomb a promise change she continued to
bush administration policies and more
and one of the way after me
now they're taking to excuse was that he
really said the name of a c_i_a_ agent
which he thought was retired
but is the one dime the c_i_a_ that they
can order the one guy who's a
whistleblower come on
so it's pretty obvious of the message
don't want to be sent bacteria who says
as bad as it was just a part was we
didn't see this kind of vindictive
selective prosecution people that we see
under obama
uh... now
he is in jail he got thirty months in
prison
he thought that he was gonna wind up
uh... in
uh... work and police in actual present
any wrote a letter from that prison
there's a serious side to it and then
there is a fascinating
slightly more humorous side to it
uh... first he says in truth
this is my punishment for blowing the
whistle on the c_i_a_'s allyl torture
program befor tell the public that
torture was official u_s_ government
policy and i think he's right about that
one other many many reasons why
president all mama
uh... has been terrible on civil
liberties
and uh... in certainly in regards to
whistle blowers
and carry out was a great example that
so he was a fire that is whether
uh... he's in federal correctional
institution in loretta pals mania now he
finds a little what's called work and he
wound up in a real present that as of
size and downsized now one of the
downsizings you've got a survivor not
present
okay and then i'll plan around the area
nation is their and you've got gangs of
all the different races there
and then you also the correctional
officers a different problem carryout
group are first of all has a problem a
c_e_o_ who apparently in every day and
will call cam perhaps is named
to said calls in
cure account carol loom teriyaki
they reacted by favored
uh... and then apparently she stopped
the one day and ask them
are you the mother fucker whose name i
can't pronounce
he said yes and then he presses
matriarchal
answers you pronounce it
they got mad he throws a wise ass comic
actresses name correctly they were paid
and actually shipped down is ceylon
life in prison
now we're just getting warms up
wait till you get a load of how he has
come two terms of the gangs in the
present
so he explains his letter
i've also had some luck in this regard
in terms of get along with those guys my
reputation preceded me in a rumor that
sort of that i was a c_i_a_ hit men
the areas was for that i was a muslim
hunter if that's awesome but the muslims
on the strength of my arabic language
skills
and oh well time sickness support from
louis farrakhan
have a lot of me as a champion of muslim
human rights
meanwhile the tides of dana lighting to
meet his unpatriotic as they are and i a
visceral dislike of the f_b_i_ which
they do as well
i have good relations with the blacks
because i've held several of them right
commutation appeals or letters to judges
and i don't read the review for
anesthetics respect me because of my
cell mates who represent a myriad eleven
drug gangs have told them to do so
so far
you know what this is great man there's
a how-to manual how to survive in prison
you know ob gyn the c_i_a_ guy is the
view c_y_a_
that's cover your ass and usually means
a you write a memo and you let people
know wasn't me
uh... hey i told i guy so this is my
c_y_a_ memo
imprison of course you buy a beat
somebody else did brierley
and apparently key factors figured out
how to be a great c_y_a_ man in prison
as well
i don't know the letter gives it away
though but im
highly it's not that i did it for the
areas is that all i am owes a lot of
mail from snapped their necks receptors
in the month
beta cell anchorman a delayed part
although a console on have erin's
by the way
my favorite rick in there
i would do the same vein
the minute i got in their amin i was a
laura like sixteen years ago i'd like
ever any legal
yeah i'll come right here freeman free
service does a lot of those let him and
i'm here all day